Guide to the Stanford University, Information Technology Services, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Information Technology Services, records
1960-1985
SC0300
Stanford University. Information Technology Services
80 Linear feet (60 boxes)
This collection contains the office files from Information Technology Services and its various predecessors, dating from 1960 to 1985. The records include correspondence, minutes, reports, proposals, contracts, budgets, manuals, bulletins, newsletters, conference proceedings, consultants' files, licensing records, computer printouts, and a small number of computer tapes. The records pertain to computer systems used in the University, the Stanford Linear Accelerator Center, and the Medical Center as well as other operations of ITS. Persons represented include Michael M. Roberts, Edward E. Shaw, William Yundt, and Colin McLeod.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
The records were received by the Stanford University Archives via administrative transfers, 1980-2010.
Information about Access
This collection is open for research; materials must be requested at least 48 hours in advance of intended use.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
Stanford University's use of computer technology for information processing began in March 1953 with the opening of the Stanford Computation Center. In April 1973, the Stanford Center for Information Processing (SCIP) was created, with Michael M. Roberts as deputy director. Its aim was to provide support for research, instruction, operations, and management. The name was later changed to the Center for Information Technology (CIT). In November 1983 four units from CIT (Computer Services, the Data Resources Group, Administrative Information Services, and Computer Operations) were combined with two other offices (Word Graphics and Communication Services) to create Information Technology Services (ITS). Edward E. Shaw was appointed director of ITS and Michael M. Roberts, deputy director.
Description of the Collection
This collection contains the office files from Information Technology Services and its various predecessors, dating from 1960 to 1985. The records include correspondence, minutes, reports, proposals, contracts, budgets, manuals, bulletins, newsletters, conference proceedings, consultants' files, licensing records, computer printouts, and a small number of computer tapes. The records pertain to computer systems used in the University, the Stanford Linear Accelerator Center, and the Medical Center as well as other operations of ITS. Persons represented include Michael M. Roberts, Edward E. Shaw, William Yundt, and Colin McLeod.
Access Terms
McLeod, Colin.; Roberts, Michael M.; Shaw, Edward E.; Stanford Linear Accelerator Center; Stanford University. Center for Information Processing.; Stanford University. Center for Information Technology.; Stanford University. Computation Center.; Stanford University. Information Technology Services; Stanford University. Medical Center.; Yundt, William H.; Interactive computer systems.
Collection Contents
- Records, Series 1
  - Peat, Marwick, Mitchell & Co. Statement of Qualifications 7/1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - SCIP Progress Report 9/1973-2/1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - SCIP Annual Report 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Preliminary Analysis of Present Computing Alternatives for Stanford University 3/1975 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - SCIP Staff Paper: Campus Facility Service & Budget Plan 5/1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - SCIP Staff Paper: Summary of 370/168 Service & Budget Planning 5/1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - SCIP Staff Paper: 1979-1980 Budget & Operating Forecast (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - SCIP Staff Paper: Background Data on Stanford Administrative Computing 4/1976 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - SCIP Staff Paper: Categories of Application Programming Effort 3/1976 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Budget Memoranda 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - OASIS Conversion Design Specification 6/1972 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - SCIP Response to EDUCOM Network Questionaire 1/1976 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Systems Software Summary Report 12/1973 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Computer Operations (Co-Op) Report Summary 10/1973 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - SCIP Annual Report 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Terminal Services 10/1969 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - “The Data Base Approach to a Management Information System” 1969 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Programming Using OASIS Terminal Services 1970 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Operation of the Sanders 720 Terminal 1970 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - QUERY Detail Specifications 1/1970 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Command Language Processor Specifications (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Generator Detail Specifications Report 5/1970 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - QUERY (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - OASIS System Description 1970 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Documentation Standards – Copy 2/1971 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Documentation Standards – Original 2/1971 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - System Test Report 6/1971 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Backup & Restart External Specifications 7/1971 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Macros 8/1971 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Gwynn Working Paper (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Users’ File 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - File Service Memoranda 1970 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - File Service Users’ Notes 1969 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Software Evaluation Form Letter (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Evaluation of File Management Software Packages 1969 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Basic Common Data Elements 4/1970 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence, General 1972 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Stanford University Pamphlet “A New Registration Plan” (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - OASIS: Student Records System 1/1971 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - OASIS: Forms, Correspondence, etc. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Audit: University Vehicle Fleet 9/1971 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Mike M. Roberts MSO Budget Presentation 10/1972 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - ACM Sigplan Notice - High Level Languages 3/1974 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - IEP Analysis & Use 6/1975 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - WICHE-PMS (Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education - Planning and Management Systems Division) Meeting 12/21-22/1970 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Instructional Costs of University Outputs 7/1971 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Audit: DHEW Grant Compliance 9/1971 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - OASIS Programmer’s Reference Booklet (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - SCC (Stanford University Computation Center) Bulletin 1970 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Project INFO: Correspondence 9/1971-8/1972 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Project INFO: Progress Report 4/1972 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Cost Analysis Manual 12/1972 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Proposal: Computer Software Marketing 7/1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Information & Management Systems General Background Material (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Audit: Purchasing & Stores Procurement Function 7/1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Audit: ACME/NIH Grant Expenditures 7/1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Audit: Tressider Memorial Union 8/1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Audit: Trade Disbursement Function 6/1971 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Audit: SUMC Fiscal Status (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - CFP (Cost Finding Principles) Project Report 9/1972 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Cost Finding Principles & Procedures Technical Report 11/1971 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Computing at Stanford- Long Term Planning Report Draft 2/1971 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Mike M. Roberts Correspondence & Memoranda 2/1972 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Mike M. Roberts Correspondence & Memoranda 3-4/1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Mike M. Roberts Correspondence & Memoranda 5-6/1972 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Mike M. Roberts Correspondence & Memoranda 7-8/1972 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Mike M. Roberts Correspondence & Memoranda 9-10/1972 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Mike M. Roberts Correspondence & Memoranda 11-12/1972 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Mike M. Roberts Correspondence & Memoranda 8-12/1970 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Mike M. Roberts Correspondence & Memoranda 11-12/1971 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Mike M. Roberts Correspondence & Memoranda 9-10/1971 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Mike M. Roberts Correspondence & Memoranda 7-8/1971 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Mike M. Roberts Correspondence & Memoranda 1-6/1971 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - CFP Task Force 6-7/1973 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - National Forum on New Planning and Management Practices in Higher Education 1/26-28/1972 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - University of Vermont Correspondence 1971 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - CFP Advisory Review Meeting 7/27/1971 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - AFIPS (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Internal Pricing Workshop 7/7-9/1971 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - WICHE CFP Task Force Meeting 4/11-14/1971 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Mike M. Roberts UC Santa Cruz Talk 1971 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - EDUCOM Conference 4/29/1971 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Machine Records Conference 5/3-5/1971 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - WICHE RRPM-2 Subcommittee Meeting 5/18-19/1971 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - National Association of College & University Business Officers Meeting 6/21/1971 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - R.L. Patrick Report 12/1970 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - IBM Purchase Orders, etc. 1973 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - OASIS: G.R.E.S.I.G.U. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - OASIS: Correspondence 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - OASIS: Illinois State University 1971 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - OASIS: “This is OASIS” Film (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - OASIS: Luther College (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - OASIS: Michigan Technical University (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - OASIS: University of Nebraska (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - OASIS: Report Form (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - OASIS: Ohio State University (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - OASIS: University of Vermont 1971-1973 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - OASIS: Inquiries (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - OASIS: University of Alberta 1972 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - OASIS: Ambassador College (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - OASIS: Manual, Original & Related (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - OASIS: “Implementation of the Educational Data Base” Traver (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - OASIS: University of Rochester 1973 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - OASIS: East Tennessee State (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - OASIS: Texas (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - OASIS: New Mexico State University (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - OASIS: Maintenance Documentation – Original (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - OASIS Implementation Guide- University of Windsor (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Project INFO: Progress Report 2/1971 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - OASIS: General Introduction 1973 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Project INFO: Introduction to Project INFO (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - QUERY Detail specifications Draft (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - “Data Bases: Uncontrollable or Uncontrolled?” Traver (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Project INFO: Renewal Background Material 1971-1973 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Project INFO: Proposal, Renewal of Ford Grant 1971-1974 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Project INFO: Second Annual Report to Ford 8/1969 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Project INFO: Narrative Grant Report 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Project INFO: Grant Interim Report 8/1969 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Project INFO: Progress Report 1/1969 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - OASIS Maintenance Documentation (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - OASIS Vol.II Distribution Notecards (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - OASIS System Manual Vol. III – Original (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Beta Sites 1974 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - OASIS System Manual Vol. II – Original (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, General (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Budget: Campus Budget Review 1973 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Budget: Medical Center Computing 1974 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Budget: SCIP Presentation 5/17/1973 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Budget: ACF 1974 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Budget: SLAC 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Budget: SLAC 1973 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Budget: SLAC 1974 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Budget: SLAC 1975 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Budget: Campus Facility 1974 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Budget: SCIP Presentation 9/28/1973 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Budget: Campus Facility 1973 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Budget: Campus Facility 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Budget: SCC 1971 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Budget: Campus Facility, General (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Budget: Campus Facility 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Budget: Campus Facility 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Personnel, Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Colin McLeod files, Series 2
  - ACM (Association for Computing Machinery) 1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - American Association of University Professors 1968 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - ACM 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Association of School Business Officials (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - CEDPA (California Educational Data Processing Association) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - CAUSE (College and University Systems Exchange) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Educational Systems Corp. – Journal of Educational Data Processing (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Fall Joint Computer Conferences 1965 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Machine Records Conferences 1965-1969 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - NACUBO (National Association of College & University Business Officers) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - WACUBO (Western Association of College & University Business Officers) 1962-1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - SPA (Systems and Procedures Association) 1961-1969 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Reference: Selection and Training of Analysts (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Reference: Student Identification System (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Reference: Textbook Information (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Reference: Time Sharing (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Educational Systems, Regional: General 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Educational Systems, Regional: AICCU (Associated Independent California Colleges & Universities) (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Educational Systems, Regional: Associated Universities, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Educational Systems, Regional: Colorado Commission on Higher Education 1969 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Educational Systems, Regional: Florida State Board of Regents (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Educational Systems, Regional: Florida State Department of Education (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Educational Systems, Regional: Graduate Research Center of the Southwest (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Educational Systems, Regional: Information Systems in Education – Project ISE (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Educational Systems, Regional: Long Beach Unified School District 1968 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Michael Roberts files, Series 3
  - Project INFO/OASIS Correspondence file 9/1972-8/1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Northern California Regional Computer Network Final Activities Report to the NSF, Prepared by SCIP 1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Final Report to the Ford Foundation on the Special Program in Education Grant to Stanford University 1965 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Final Report; Pilot Test of the NCHEMS Resource Requirements Prediction Model Version 1.2. S.U. Management Systems Office 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - S.U. Medical Center Proposed Service Facility. Prepared by Stanford University Hospital Data Processing 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Computation Center Staff Meeting Minutes 1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Budget: Salary 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Proposals: A Proposal to the NSF to Establish the Stanford Laser Science Center as a Regional Instrumentation Facility 1977 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Operations Study: Projected 158 Workload 4/16/1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Project INFO: The Design and Testing of an Integrated Computer System for the Administrative Processes of the University. Progress Report, April 1972 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Computer Facilities Merger Memoranda 1972-73 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Subcommittee on Administrative Computing 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Subcommittee on Research and Instruction (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Reorganization - SCIP (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Reorganization - SCC (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Vice Provost for Medical Affairs - Clayton Rich (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence - V.P. Augsberger 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence - Gene Franklin 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence - W.F. Massy 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence - W.F. Massy 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Sale of Equipment - General 1967 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- W. H. Yundt files, Series 4
  - Procurement, Brokers: General 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Procurement, Brokers: CMI (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Procurement, Brokers: Dataware Marketing, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Procurement, Brokers: American Used Computer Corp. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Procurement, Brokers: General 1977 -1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Technical Reports: Software 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Technical Reports: Systems: Systems Change Notices (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Technical Reports: Software Convergence Group (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Rates, Computer 370/168 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Utilization: SLAC 1974-1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Utilization: Academic Computing Income 1968-1973 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Stanford Computer Use Survey Interim Report 1969 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Technical Reports: ACME (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Technical Reports: AAG 1977 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Printing Office 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Planning, Short Range: Strike Contingency 1976 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Planning, Short Range: Software Coordination 1977 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Planning, Short Range: Technical 1972-1976 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Policy: SLAC 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Personnel: Youth Opportunity Program (YOP) 1970-1975 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Boys Town Center for Youth Development at Stanford 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Planning, Long Range: BALLOTS Center (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Planning, Long Range: Computer (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Planning, Short Range: Academic Computing 1970-1977 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Planning, Short Range: SCIP 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Planning, Short Range: Systems Software 1973-1979 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Planning, Short Range: Medical Computing 1974 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Contracts: Standard Computer Corporation 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Contracts: 360/67 Use Agreement - 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Committees: SCIP Welfare and Recreation Committee (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Committees: Committee on Software Coordination 1978 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Committees: SCIP Executive Committee Minutes 1973-1977 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Committees: SCIP Publications Committee 1973-1977 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Proposals: ACME 1973 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Proposals: SPIRES 1970 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Proposals: SLAC 1974-195 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Accounting: SLAC (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Accounting: Hospital Computing 1973-1977 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Accounting: SPIRES (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Accounting: SPIRES/BALLOTS 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Accounting: 370/158 1975 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Accounting: ACME 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Audit: ACME (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Audit: SLAC (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Budget: SLAC 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Budget: SLAC 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - SCIP: VeFAC Final Report 1976 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-1983-080
  - CONTEXT: A CONTEXT Primer 1981 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - CONTEXT: Troubleshooting Guide (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - CONTEXT: Getting Started on CONTEXT (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - CONTEXT: Archiving (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - CONTEXT: Progress Reports 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - SCRIBE Seminar 11/6/1981 (6 U-Matic Videotapes) (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-1983-147
  - Stanford Medical Computing Newsletter 1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 158 Standards Manual 1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Stanford University Advisory Committee on Computer Science & Computing Meeting 3/23-25/1983 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - SUN Workstation – A Terminal System for the SU Network 1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Requirements for SPIRES II 4/1971 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - PAC Meeting 2/10-11/1982 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Reports: SCIP Annual Report to the Federal Government 8/31/1979 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Reports: SCIP Annual Report 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Reports: SCIP Annual Report 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Reports: SCIP Annual Report 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Reports: SCIP Annual Report 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Reports: SCIP Annual Report to the Federal Government 8/31/1974 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Report: SCIP Progress Report 9/1973-2/1974 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - WYLBUR Tutorial 1975 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Plan & Configuration for Equipment Acquisition 4/1976 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Central Computing System for Stanford University (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Proposal: NSF 1966 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Sponsored Projects: Computer System “DO 1” 1980 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Issues Facing SCIP Report 1977 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - SCIP Picture Book 6/1976 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Administrative Data Processing Plan 1966-1970 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Reports: Position Paper Advocating an All-Digital Data Communication Network 1975 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Proposal: NSF Educational Computer Network 1971 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Guide to Computer Performance Reporting 11/1972 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - SCIP Newsletter 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - ACS (Academic Computing Services) Bulletin 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Encina Computing Services Bulletin 1974 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Indices, Campus Facility Bulletin (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - SCIP Planning & Documentation 1974 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - RLIN/BALLOTS Newsletter 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-1984-003
  - Activities 1/1981
  - AFIPS (American Federation of Information Processing Societies) Conference Proceedings, Vol. 39 1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - AFIPS Conference Proceedings, Vol. 43 1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - AFIPS Conference Proceedings, Vol. 47 1978 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - AFIPS Conference Proceedings, Vol. 49 1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - AFIPS Conference Proceedings, Vol. 52 1983 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Society for Management Information Systems Conference 1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Project INFO: OASIS University of Windsor 1976 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Project INFO: OASIS General Introduction 1973 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Project INFO: OASIS System Description 1970 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Project INFO: OASIS Conversion Design Specifications 1972 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Project INFO: OASIS Inquiries (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Project INFO: OASIS Installation Instructions (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Project INFO: OASIS Svobodova/Columbia Performance Monitors Documentation 1974 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Project INFO: OASIS System Manual Vol. II Applications Programmer's Guide (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Accounting Microfiche 1975-1979 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Project INFO: OASIS System Manual Vol. III System Maintenance Guide (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Project INFO: Correspondence, Ford Grants, Financial Reports, OASIS Newsletters, Progress Reports, Publicity 1968-1976 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Project INFO: Final Ford Report, Ford General, Budget Statements 1976 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Medical Computing Planning Document & Status Report 6/1973 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Stanford University Medical Center, Long Range Financial Plan 6/1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - HCS (Hospital Computing Service) Standards Manual 1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Medical Computing Budgets 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Medical Computing Services: Bulletins, Newsletters 1967-1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Medical Computing Services: Time-Oriented Databank User's Manual Part 1&2 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Reports 1980 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - SUMEX (Stanford University Medical Experimental Computing Facility) Proposal 3/1973 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - ACME progress reports 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - ACME Special Research Annual Reports 1967-1970 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - ACME Annual Reports 1971-1973 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Proposal: Technical Evaluation Group Patient Accounting System 8/1981 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - SUMEX Annual Report 6/1982 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - ATD System Selection Arthur Anderson Report 3/1982 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Medical Records (PCC) Proposal 12/1975 (Box 4, Folder 4)